

# Alejandro Yunes

Front-end Dev.

With 4 years of experience in IT administration and more than 4 years in software development, I have acquired a variety of relevant skills that includes a in-depth knowledge of Javascript, React, HTML, CSS, UI/UX, and Windows server architecture.

## **Professional Resume**

## Experience

2020 - Current

Inxeption

Front End Developer

Front-End with React, TypeScript, Sass, GraphQL. Feature development and bug fixing. Agile scrum methodology.

2019 - 2020

Inaltect S.A.S.

Software Analyst

Developed and maintained mobile bank app with OutSystems framework and custom Javascript. Also, worked on second project with React, TypeScript, Sagas.

2017 - 2019

Freelancer

Fullstack Developer

Development of SPA with NextIS, MongoDB, and styled-components.

2014 - 2017

GHR South America S.AS.

Systems Engineer

Support T-Systems internal app, and system admin.

2012 - 2013

Oralaser Clínica las Vegas

Systems Engineer

Management, monitoring installed IT systems infrastructure. LAN Admin: HP ProLiant G5, G6 Win Server 2008R2 – DC, AD, DNS, DHCP, security policies, antivirus console, wireless end user support.

### Education

2010

Dutchess Community College Information Management

Associates in Computer Science

2007

Beacon High School

#### Contact

1

https://github.com/alejandroyunes



https://stackoverflow.com/users/8133300/alejandro-yunes



https://www.linkedin.com/in/alejandro-yunes-bb562720a/